（忆往昔）
弗兰克·德弗罗
Frank Devereaux.
傻子加疯子
He's a jackass and a lunatic.
他还是个监控专家
He is also a surveillance expert.
弗兰克 好好查查理查德·罗曼
"Hey, Frank, go dig up some dirt on Richard Roman."
那天晚上 我所有的IP都用报废了
That night, I was burned off every I.P. I had.
电话有人监听 房子受到监控
Ears on my phones, eyes on my house…
是迪克派人监视你吗
Dick's got people watching you?
弗兰克 别开枪 我们要进去了
Frank! Don't shoot! We're coming in.
老弗兰克知道的太多了
Who's to say this ain't the day.
谁知道他们今天会不会来下毒手
they come for old Frank who knew too much.
鲍比
Bobby!
你的时辰到了
Your time is up.
鲍比 你从死神手里逃脱了
Bobby. You ran away from your reaper?
你们好 孩子们
Hi, boys.
- 鲍比 - 你们看的到我吗
- Bobby. - You can see me?
你是怎么想的 鲍比
What were you thinking, Bobby?
我们还要活儿要干
We still have work to do.
但这是不对的 你心里清楚
It's not right. You know that.
我怎么想的啊
What was I thinking?
- 你觉得我们该怎么办 - 我不知道
- So, what do you think we should do? - I don't know.
世间万物都该有终结
Everything is supposed to end.
他应该…
You know, he was supposed…
可现在
Now…
这样能有好结果吗
What are the odds this ends well?
能有吗
What are the odds?
（如今）
知道了 好吧 谢谢你帮忙找
Yeah, I hear you. All right, well, thanks for looking.
好 再见
Yep. Bye.
诺拉也看不出考古挖掘点的套路
So, Nora didn't see any pattern to the dig sites either.
是啊 因为根本就没有共同之处
Yeah, 'cause they got nothing in common.
我从当地传说也没查到线索
And I got nothing from local lore.
上上下下都查遍了
50 miles in every direction of all of them.
好像那些真就只是…
I mean, it's like they're just…
陈年的泥巴
old dirt.
迪克在找什么
What's Dick looking for?
别紧张 小混球
Hey, hey, go easy, you idjits.
抱歉突然冒出来吓你们
Sorry for the jump scare.
这是怎么个原理
So how does this work, huh?
我一拧开壶盖 你就像灯神一样钻出来了吗
I leave the cap off and you just genie your way out?
要是有那么简单就好了
I wish it were that easy.
问题是…
The thing is …
鲍比
Bobby?
妈的 想集中注意力真难
Damn it. It's hard to stay focused.
我还是有点累
I'm still kind of worn out.
作为一个死人来说 你最近相当忙
You've been pretty busy for a dead guy.
好吧 听我说
All right. Listen.
我不知道离我下次鬼休克还有多久
I-I don't know how long before my next ghost nap,
所以咱们就直接切入正题
so let's just skip to the skinny …
我给你们的那串数字
Those numbers I gave you.
智兹维尔那片空地吗
The empty lot in Cheeseville?
那里不会空太久了
Yeah, well, it ain't gonna be empty for long.
我瞟过一眼迪克的宏伟计划
I got a gander at Dick's big plan,
就在他枪杀我之前
right before he Lincolned me.
他们准备要动工了 现在是几月
They're breaking ground … what month is this?
四月
Uh, April.
已经开始动工了
Ground's broke.
他们在做调查
They're surveying.
他们正准备建个什么东西
They're getting ready to build something.
- 要建什么 - 问得好
- Build what? - Exactly.
建什么
What?
咱们在这抱怨的时候 他们已经在动工了
They're building as we're yammering.
你自己去看 没关系
Check it out yourself. It's all right.
你们之所以没注意 是因为最近几天
I mean, you guys missed it because you've been kind of busy.
你们一直在忙着杀鬼
killing ghosts the past few days.
但迪克要着手经营「加工食品」
But Dick is about to get into the Soylent Green business.
网站上显示他们要建生物技术实验室 对吧
That site'll show you they're building a biotech lab, right?
妹的的生物技术
Biotech my ass.
那个操蛋地方是个顶尖水准的屠宰场
That sucker is a state-of-the-art slaughterhouse.
人为刀俎 我们为鱼肉
And we're the beef.
即使是对迪克 这也略微大胆了点吧
Don't you think that's a little bold, even for Dick?
我敢说没人会发现
I bet you no one will even notice,
因为他首先会用火鸭鸡三明治一类的快餐
'cause first, he's gonna dumb us all down.
把我们的智商拉低
with turducken-style munchies.
让我们变得温顺
Make us docile.
毒物在肉里
It's in the meat.
自从那次惨败之后 我们就没去过比格森
We haven't been to Biggerson's since that whole fiasco.
比格森 他买下了一长串快餐店
Biggerson's? He's bought a list of joints 10 pages long.
接下来 他会帮我们治愈疾病
Next, he's gonna cure us.
什么疾病
Cure us of what?
所有致命性疾病 癌症 艾滋 心脏病
All the biggies … cancer, AIDS, heart disease.
他们有一处类似于干细胞研究所的机构
Let's just say they got an affinity for stem-cell research.
那个利维坦房地产公司
The, uh, Leviathan real-estate mooks.
不是说要建抗癌中心吗
building that cancer center.
这里要建科研中心
It's going to be a research center.
研究啥
Research for what?
他们已经不在捕猎了
They're not hunting anymore.
他们要用基因改造创造完美的群体
They're engineering the perfect herd.
首剂就能作用于其DNA
With the very first dose, it starts to work on their DNA,
减慢他们的新陈代谢 导致体重增加
slowing their metabolism, causing weight gain,
还能抑制他们的情感波动
and dampening their emotional range,
让他们洋洋自得
which makes them perfectly complacent.
我们对付过的不少货色
Now, we've gone up against plenty …
喜欢在林子里吃人
Liked to eat a few folk in the woods.
这次情况不同
This ain't that.
他们这是要把我们从食物链最顶端踹下来
This is about knocking us off the top of the food chain.
他们利维坦要永远住在这里
This is about them Levis living here forever,
还是少数人高高在上
one-percenter style,
而把我们排挤到
while we march our dopey, fat asses.
在各处新建的死亡集中营里那种
down to the shiny new death camps at every corner.
收到一封邮件
It's an e-mail…
弗兰克发来的
From Frank.
弗兰克还活着吗
Frank's alive?
那个混球 总是抢我风头
That jackass, always stealing my thunder.
萨姆和迪恩
"Sam and Dean,
如果你们读到这封信 说明我已经死了
if you're reading this, I'm dead…"
或者情况更糟
"…or worse.
这封邮件是为了提醒你们
"This e-mail was sent because some prince.
现在正有人试图黑进我的硬盘
"is trying to hack into my hard drive right this second.
除非那是你们 否则你们就有麻烦了
So unless it's you, you got trouble."
好吧 我的硬盘里装满了机密信息
Okay."My drive is full of compromising info.
你们的新化名 住所 存车地
Your new aliases, hangouts, where you stored your car…"
爱车
Baby?
尽管他对硬盘进行了层层加密
Even though he encrypted the crap out of his drive,
但我们要做好心理准备 有人最终会黑进去
he says we should assume that someone can hack into it eventually.
他在上面安装了追踪装置
He did put a tracking device in it.
好 看看弗兰克的硬盘在哪儿
All right, let's see where Frank's drive is.
（找到硬盘 理查德·罗曼企业）
太棒了
Perfect.
就在敌人的大本营
It's in the middle of the death star.
[邪恶力量 第7季第20集]
（五小时前）
（美国保守党）
昨晚过得怎么样
How'd it go last night?
查理
Charlie,
让我通过你间接体验生活是你的道义责任
it's a moral imperative you let me live vicariously through you.
无图无真相 对吧
Pictures or it didn't happen, right?
你竟然在慈善活动上钓到人
You hooked up at a charity benefit?
如果在生殖权慈善宴会上都没有艳遇
If you can't score at a reproductive rights function,
那在别的地方也没戏
then you simply cannot score.
等等 这合法吗
Wait. Is that legal?
我们都是成年人 你情我愿有何不可
We were two consenting adults.
不 我是指那个
No. That.
（感谢您的捐款）
你为什么要用公司电脑做违法乱纪的事
Why do you insist on breaking the law on company property?
公司的网速比较快
Mmm, faster internet connection here.
如果皮特发现了 他会炒了你
Oh, well, if Pete finds out, he's gonna fire you…
或报警逮捕你
Or get you arrested.
泰迪熊皮特吗 拜托
Teddy bear Pete? Please.
你也知道这事我都干了一个月了
You know I've been doing this for like a month.
我能掩盖行踪 哈利
I can cover my tracks, Harry.
相信我
Trust me.
查理
Charlie!
立刻来我办公室
My office. Now.
- 我爱你 - 我知道
- I love you. - I know.
查理·布兰博利
Charlie Bradbury?
我是迪克
Dick.
请坐
Sit.
查理 我执掌大权的时间
Charlie, I've been running things for, well,
似乎比人类的历史还长
feels like since before the dawn of man.
我一直有个梦想
Always had a vision.
如今我的梦想触手可及
I'm close to realizing that dream.
不是我自夸 这世界就是我的餐盘
I don't want to brag, but the world is my dinner plate.
我不想让任何事危及我的梦想
And I don't want anything to jeopardize that…
绝不会让一颗老鼠屎坏了一锅粥
Definitely not the actions of one tiny, little person.
先生 我可以处理好的 求你不要解雇我
Sir, sir, I can fix this. Please… please don't fire me.
她在说什么
What's she talking about?
你是说黑掉超政行委（美国专门负责做竞选的组织）的事吗
Is that about hacking those super PACs?
真是太厉害了
'cause that was adorable.
告诉我 一个高中辍学生
Tell me, how does a high-school dropout.
怎么会成为罗曼公司最聪明的人之一呢
become one of the brightest minds at Roman, Inc.?
说实话
Um…honestly… historically,
我一直都看不惯当权人
I've had this problem with… with authority…
无意冒犯
No offense…
我意识到只有尽可能成为一个不可或缺的人
So I realized the only way to get away with being me.
才能自由地做我自己
was to be as indispensable as possible.
抱歉
Sorry.
你似乎让我的人生完整了 查理
You're kind of completing me right now, Charlie.
你有灵气
You have that spark,
正是这种灵气才让人类如此与众不同
that thing that makes humans so special.
不是每个人都有的
Not everyone has it, you know.
没有灵气的人可以被取代
Those people… they can be replaced.
但像你这样的人 是无法复制的
But people like you… are impossible to copy.
复制
C-copy?
我在夸你呢
Take the compliment.
这东西属于一个叫弗兰克·德弗罗的人
This belonged to one Frank Devereaux.
他觉得他能让这整个公司垮台
Thought he could bring down the whole company.
他没做的 让他不能得逞吧
He was wrong. Let's keep him wrong.
不管你们小青年怎么说 这东西加密了
It's encrypted, or whatever you crazy kids say these days.
破解密码然后交给我
Break it open and bring it to me.
好的 我这就去办 谢谢
Yeah, I'm on it. And… and thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
你有三天时间 失败的话就滚蛋
You have three days or you're fired.
谈话愉快
Good talk.
这都是真的吗
Is this real life?
迪克·罗曼给了我一个任务
Dick Roman gave me an assignment.
是 好事吗
Is that…good?
就是说索伦之眼正盯着我呢
It means the Eye of Sauron is on me.
你需要什么的话 我就在夏尔
Well, if you need anything, I'll be back in the Shire.
好了 小赫 只剩我们俩了
All right, H. It's just you and me now.
（拒绝访问）
下盘国际象棋吧
How about a nice game of chess?
等等
Wait a second.
不是吧
Seriously?
「战棋」
"WarGames"?
（你好猎鹰教授）
来玩游戏吧
Shall we play a game, bitches?
能比《消失的密室》难搞吗
That was hardly the Chamber of Secrets, right?
（想得美 你个软蛋）
要从头再来了
And back to square one.
看看弗兰克的硬盘在哪儿
Let's see where Frank's drive is.
太棒了
Perfect.
就在敌人的大本营
It's in the middle of the death star.
好吧 去芝加哥
All right, well, off to Chicago.
等等 孩子们 你们不能就这样闯进去
No, wait, boys, you can't just break in.
他们认得你们
They know your mugs.
不如我们把酒瓶邮寄过去
What if we mailed in the flask?
我这个鬼能在那里通行无阻
Then I could ghost through the joint.
迪克又不能杀我两次
I mean, it's not like Dick can kill me twice.
怎么 你有更好的计划
What, you got a better plan?
拜托 就因为我死了
Come on. Just because I'm dead.
不代表我不知道怎么干活
doesn't mean I don't know how to do my damn job.
鲍比 那是迪克的办公室
Bobby, that's Dick's office.
我猜萨姆是想说
I think what Sam's trying to say is,
如果你遇上迪克
what happens if you run into Dick.
想找他报仇 怎么办
and, you know… go vengeful.
这可不是你说放下就能放下的
You know it's not something you can just shake off.
拜托 稍稍信任我一点吧
Come on. Give me some credit.
难道我就应该坐冷板凳干着急吗
What, I'm supposed to just ride the pine?
抱歉 鲍比
Sorry, Bobby.
你昨晚回家了吗
Did you go home last night?
我去倒两杯咖啡来
I'll get us some coffee.
估计你那杯会想加点可卡因吧
I assume you want some crack in yours.
没错 谢了
Yes, please.
（允许访问）
总算好了
Finally.
这家伙是谁
Who is this d-bag?
（理查德·罗曼企业）
别手贱
Don't do it.
罗曼说直接交给他
Roman said to bring it right to him.
你说得对 小赫 你总是对的
You're right, H. You're always right.
利维坦是什么
What the frak's a Leviathan?
「关于利维坦 你需要知道
"The thing to know about Leviathan.
这些怪物十分古老
is these monsters are as old as time,
是最强大的…
strong as all get-out…
硼酸钠 也就是硼砂
Sodium borate… commonly known as borax.
关键是砍头
Decapitation is the key.
然后把头放进盒子
Then put that head in a box.
它们是怪物中的战斗机
These are the superman of monsters.
- 来自于炼狱黑洞 - 有本事
- from the black hole of purgatory. - …send it to the moon.
送去月亮上
if you can.
- 它们可以变形 - 如果能杀死他们
- "They can shapeshift, - If they die…
- 拥有你的脸 - 也肯定不易
- take your face, - they don't die easy.
你的记忆 与你相关的一切
your memory … the works.
老大是迪克·罗曼先生
The top boss is Mr. Dick Roman.
他是最高指挥「
He runs the show."
「割伤它们就会看到黑色胶状物
"Cut one, you see black goo.
我们是掉进了奇境
We're through the looking glass.
血是黑的 黑的就是血
Blood is black, and black is blood.
别回头
Don't turn your back.
逃离你所在的楼 逃出国「
Get out of the building. Get out of the county."
怎么样了
How goes it?
我肯定是花了一整天时间黑进了疯人院
Pretty sure I spent the last 24 hours hacking into a loony bin.
皮特呢
Where's Pete?
可能溜到车库去抽烟了
Uh, probably snuck down to the garage for a smoky treat.
硬盘进展如何
How's it going with that drive?
很好
Uh, great.
查理整晚都待在这
Charlie was here all night.
那个硬盘对我很重要
You know, that drive's very important to me.
我得安排人替我看着
I'm gonna want a watchful eye kept.
我会帮你看着的
Well, I will do just that.
不 你不会
No. You won't.
布鲁斯·斯普林斯汀（歌手）
Bruce Springsteen,
伊莱·曼宁（橄榄球选手） 我们的小查理
Eli Manning, our own little Charlie…
你知道他们是什么吗
You know what they are?
无法取代的人
Irreplaceable.
你充其量就是蒂姆·蒂博（橄榄球选手）
You're more of a Tim Tebow,
乔·拜登（奥巴马竞选对手）
Toe Biden type.
身上没有灵气
You got no spark in you.
事实上 你一无是处
In fact, there's nothing in you…
只能做达里尔的晚餐了
except Daryl's dinner.
皮特 抱歉没说一声就走了
Hey, Pete, sorry I left without telling you.
不 就是有些不舒服
No, I just wasn't… feeling well.
就是 女人的问题
It's a…lady thing.
我明天一早就去
I will be in first thing.
挂了哦 肚子疼
Got to go… cramps.
没事的 我不会伤害你的
It's all right. I'm not gonna hurt you.
离我远点 你们个
Get away from me, you…
易形者
Shapeshifter!
我们不是易形者
Look, we're not shapeshifters.
娘亲啊
Jesus!
我们不是利维坦
Look, we're not Leviathans, okay?
要我们证明吗
You want us to prove it?
你知道硼砂能给他们造成什么伤害吧
You know what borax does to them?
萨姆
Sam?
轮到你了
Your turn.
很好
Good.
你们到底是谁
Who the hell are you guys?
你们是说 你们是斩妖除魔的猎人
So you are saying you guys're the monster hunters.
那就是说 还有其他的妖怪喽
So, there are other monsters?
别说 算了 当我没问
Stop. Never mind. Just shh.
好吧 我知道你们是怎么找到这个硬盘的
Okay, I get how you tracked the drive …
通过GPS 可那个硬盘还在办公室
straight GPS … but it's still at the office.
你们是怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
见鬼 居然黑了我的网络摄像头
Aw! Son of a gun jacked my webcam?!
弗兰克就这德行
Welcome to Frank.
他还真厉害得吓人
It's creepy, I'll give it to him.
你们是说 他盘上的东西全是真的
So you're telling me everything he had on his drive is true.
而且远不止这些
That and more.
等等 你花了多久破解掉弗兰克的盘的
Wait. How long did it take you to crack into Frank's drive?
差不多一天吧
A day or so.
有什么是你破解不掉的吗
Is there anything you can't hack into?
迄今还没有
Not yet.
迪克·罗曼的电子邮件呢
How about Dick Roman's E-mail?
我为什么要…
Why would I…
他也是其中之一
Oh. He's one of them.
不准确 他是大Boss
No. Uh, he's their leader.
他们想怎么样
So what's the end game …
偷走我们的资源 把我们变成奴隶
steal our resources, make us some slaves?
全球超值套餐 我们就是那个「餐」
Planet-wide value meal. We're the meat.
你们不是…开玩笑的吧
You can't be…serious.
好吧 好吧 我们开始吧
Okay. All right. Let's do this.
我要查什么
What am I looking for?
先查查关于考古挖掘点的内容
Well, for starters, uh, anything about archaeological dig sites.
《夺宝奇兵》的那种吗
Like Indiana Jones stuff?
我们只知道迪克把整个地球都挖了个遍
All we know is that Dick has been digging all over the world,
我们要知道他在找什么
And we need to know what he's looking for.
话说 我这周还蛮顺利的呢
You know, I was having a really good week.
我遇到个人 还下载了罗宾的新专辑
I met someone, downloaded the new Robyn album.
可以说顺风顺水
Everything was coming up me.
糟了
Oh, crap.
我们知道这很糟糕
Look, we get it sucks.
不 不是那个 是这个
No, not that. This.
迪克的电子邮件不在公司的服务器上
Dick's E-mail isn't on the company server.
在他办公室的私人服务器上
It's on a private one, in his office.
什么意思
Meaning?
除非你有他的电话或者就在他的办公室里
Can't get in it unless you have his phone.
不然进不去
or you're at his desk.
你是说如果我们能进去迪克的办公室
So you're saying that if we're inside Dick's office,
就能黑进他的电子邮件
then we can hack into his E-mail?
你不行 除非像…
You can't. Only someone like…
打死我都不去
But I sure as hell ain't doing it.
我就是本分地工作…
I am doing my job and…
硬盘上的东西我全看过了
What are the chances I see everything on that drive.
迪克会留我活口吗
and Dick lets me live anyway?
我想你懂的
I think you know.
那我就删掉硬盘上的东西 好保护我们三个
So I erase the drive first, protect me and you.
然后继续过我的小日子 对吗
Then I go back to my old life, right?
- 怎么了 - 没那么简单
- What? - It's not that easy.
你已经被迪克盯上了
You're on Dick's radar,
也就是说你没有小日子可继续了
which means you don't have an old life anymore.
我会死的
I'm gonna die.
当初该去谷歌的
I should have taken that job at Google.
听着 查理 如果你不干也没关系
Look, Charlie, it's okay if you can't do it.
你又不是你想做的
I mean, you didn't volunteer for this.
完全没有 一点没错
Totally. Exactly.
但我现在想做了
But now I volunteer.
什么
What?
反正我也得回去删掉弗兰克硬盘上的东西
I got to go back in anyways to wipe Frank's drive.
那就顺便闯下迪克的办公室好了
Might as well break into Dick's office, too.
你确定
Are you sure?
不确定 可这些怪物会吃掉我认识的所有人
No. But these things are gonna eat everyone I know.
混蛋才袖手旁观呢
What kind of douche bag stands by for that?
话说回来 在现实生活中我从没有闯过
However, I have never broken into anything.
任何地方 那…有什么计划吗
in real life before, so…plan?
有蓝牙吗
Got a bluetooth?
有
Yeah.
你能进入安全系统吗
Security system … can you get into that?
我能随意控制我们需要的任何监控摄像头
I can reroute any surveillance cameras we need.
很好 那我们就从那个入手吧
All right. Let's start with that.
你有进入大楼的出入卡吗
Do you have a key card to get in the building?
算有吧
Uh, yeah.
我没办法复制出入卡 但我能伪造磁条
I can't duplicate it, but I can make a fake backing.
进展如何
How's it going?
很好 她把什么都搞定了
Great, since she set all this up.
快过来看
Um, look.
看到没
See this?
我能让每个监视器循环播放事先录好的画面
I can put each camera on a prerecorded loop.
这样的话 她就能有十五分钟时间
Once I do that, she'll have 15 minutes.
十五分钟时间又不多
15 minutes ain't a lot of time.
是不多
No.
她说如果黑进他的台式机要超过一刻钟
She said if it took longer to hack his desktop,
那她活该被吃
then she deserved to be eaten.
我喜欢这姑娘
I like her.
等等 是不是…
Wait. Is that…
见鬼
Son of a bitch.
- 怎么了 - 看她的背包
- What? - Look at her bag.
是鲍比
Bobby.
等等 你觉得他是
Wait. Y-you think he …
我们让他别妄动 他却搭了个顺风车
Hitched a ride after we told him to cool his jets?
对 他怎么想的
Yeah. What the hell's he thinking?
他没好好想
He's not.
那我们怎么办 取消行动吗
So what do we do … call the whole thing off?
我们就这一次机会
We only got one shot at this.
查理 我是迪恩
Charlie, it's Dean.
你在唱歌吗
Are you singing?
我一紧张就会唱歌 别对我指手画脚
I sing when I'm nervous. Don't judge me.
我什么都不说
Judgment-free zone.
听着 看下你背包边上的口袋
Listen, uh, check the side pocket in your bag.
谢谢
Thank you.
真贴心
Mmm. Good idea.
不用谢
Yeah, no problem.
那个东西差不多是个传家宝
Look, that's, uh, kind of a family heirloom.
是个好运符 你可别丢了
It's a good-luck charm, okay, so don't lose it.
收到
Copy that.
好了
Okay.
我们开始行动吧
Let's do this.
查理
Uh, Charlie?
我动不了
I'm having a hard time moving.
你可以的
You can do this.
我我不是间谍
Uh, I'm … I'm not a spy.
不行 我办不到 我办不到
No, I can't do it. I can't do it.
我办不到 我不行啊
I can't do it. I can't.
- 查理 我是萨姆 - 对不起 萨姆
- Charlie, hey, it's Sam. - I'm sorry, Sam.
- 对不起 我只是 - 没关系
- I'm sorry. I-I just … - It's okay.
听着 《哈利波特》里面你最喜欢谁
Uh, listen, w-who's your favorite "Harry Potter" character?
赫敏
Uh, Hermione.
赫敏啊
Hermione.
好吧 小天狼星布莱克遇到麻烦的时候
Well, uh, all right, did Hermione run.
或者伏地魔攻击霍格沃茨的时候
when Sirius Black was in trouble.
赫敏会转身逃跑吗
or when Voldemort attacked Hogwarts?
- 你在开玩笑 - 闭嘴
- Seriously? - Shut it.
不会 当然不会
No, of course not.
她会怎么做
What did she do?
她会击败困难
She kicked ass.
事实上几乎在每本书里都是她救了哈利
She actually saves Harry in practically every book.
- 可她最终却跟… - 回到正题
- And then she ends up with the wrong … - Uh, stay on track.
所以说 她会击败困难 对吧
Okay, so she kicked ass, right?
那么你会怎么做呢
So, then, what are you gonna do?
击败困难
I'm gonna kick it in the ass.
好姑娘
Good girl.
你真行 邓布利呆（借用《哈利波特》里Dumbledo校长的名字）
Oh, you go, Dumble-dork.
我进来了
I'm in.
我一直想说这句话
I've always wanted to say that.
时间紧迫
You're on the clock.
快行动
Move.
这儿有个大块头保安 堵住了去路
Hey, there's a big-ass guard up here, blocking the door.
我该怎么办
What do I do?
等他走开
Just wait him out.
看来他是不准备走了
He's not going anywhere.
你每天都在那儿上班
Okay, uh, you work there every day.
- 你应该认识他吧 - 算是吧
- Doyouknow the guy? - I guess.
我见过他 但是没有讲过话
I mean, I've seen him. I've never talked to him.
好的 那么你们打照面时 他是盯着你看
Okay, when you've seen him, does he look at you,
还是扫你一眼就过去了
or does he just kind of slide his eyes by?
看没看我 不清楚
Um…eye contact? I don't know.
他总是笑那么一下
He always kind of smiles a bit.
- 我不是很… - 很好
- I don't really … Good.
你现在就直接朝他走过去
What you're gonna do is you're gonna walk right up to him,
色诱他然后混过去
and you're gonna flirt your way past.
办不到 我不喜欢他这类的
I can't. He's not my type.
那你就装装相
You're gonna have to play through that.
因为他不是女人
As in he's not a girl.
假装他波涛汹涌
Pretend he has boobs.
你在帮倒忙
Worse.
我想想 你有没有纹身
I don't know. Um… do you have any tattoos?
露出来给他瞧上一眼
Give him a little sneak peek there.
纹身总是性感的
All tattoos are sexy.
我纹的是穿奴隶比基尼的莉亚公主
Mine is princess leia in a slave bikini.
跨在一个二十面骰子上
straddling a 20-sided die.
我在动漫展后喝醉了纹的
I was drunk. It was comic-con.
我也干过这种事
We've all been there.
我指导你怎么做
Okay, I'm gonna walk you through this.
面带笑容
Start with a smile.
放松 查理
Relax, Charlie.
想象你刚回到家
You just got home,
斯嘉丽·约翰逊正在那儿等你
and Scarlett Johansson's waiting for you.
能为你效劳吗 女士
Can I help you, miss?
你好 比尔 我是信息部的查理
Hey…Bill. Charlie from I.T.
通宵工作呢 辛苦了
Oh. Burning the midnight oil, huh?
你不也是嘛 你是不是总泡健身馆
Just like you … I mean, when you're not at the gym.
你看着像把休息时间都花在健身上了
What, do you work out with all your free time?
我每星期都尽量腾出三天去健身
I try to get to the gym at least three days a week.
我努力减回最佳身材
You know, just trying to get back to my fighting weight,
效果不错啊 你看起来棒极了
You know? It shows. You look amazing.
It shows. You look amazing.
这话我没说过
This never happened.
你平时都做些什么呢
Do you ever do anything else with your free time,
带不带女孩子去喝酒啊
like take a girl out for a drink?
你平时都做些什么呢
You do anything else with your free time,
- 带不带女孩子去喝酒啊 - 别笑了 萨姆
- like take a girl out for a drink? - Stop laughing, Sammy.
别笑了 萨姆
Stop laughing, Sammy.
你不知道那个酒吧吗
Um…y-you don't know that bar …
别笑了 萨姆
Stop Laughing Sammy?
那地方棒极了
That place is bringing sexy back.
- 别说了 查理 - 挺方便的
- Stop talking, Charlie! - Which is easy,
他们还能开发票
'cause they kept the receipt.
别说了 查理
Stop talking, charlie. Right.
那有空我们出去喝一杯怎么样
So, um, y-you were saying about going out, drinks?
那好啊 太棒了
Um…yeah, yeah. That'd be great.
那就这样说定了
Cool. Pencil that in.
你能帮我个忙吗
Hey, can I ask you a favor?
楼下的女厕所脏死了
The ladies' room downstairs is nasty.
我能用这边高管的洗手间吗
Can I use the exec washroom to powder my nose?
好啊 没问题 沿着走廊走
Yeah, yeah. Why not? Um, it's right down the hall.
右边的第一个房间
It's the first door on the right.
恶心死我了
I feel dirty.
我也差不多好吗 姐姐
You and me both, sister.
我到了
The eagle is landing.
我先挂电话了
Going radio-silent.
出来的时候告诉我们
Let us know when you're out.
那我们就干等吗
So, guess we just wait?
对
Yeah.
你的密码是「痣在逼得」
Your password is "w1nn1ng" with two 1's?
好了 我是绝地大师
Okay. Let's Yoda this.
你好
Hey, you!
你在这儿干嘛
What are you doing in here?
你不是说左边的第一个房间吗
You said first door on the left, right?
我说的是右边第一个
No, I said first door on the right.
我真傻 我太健忘了
Oh! Silly me. I am always forgetting things.
你知道我忘了干什么吗
Do you know what else I forgot to do?
给你我的电话
Give you my phone number.
我们不该进这里的
Uh, we really shouldn't be in here.
罗曼先生不喜欢别人进他的办公室
Mr. Roman doesn't like people in his office.
必须的 你看过他的厕所吗
I'm sure. Have you seen his bathroom?
我要走了
Got to go.
给我电话
Call me.
这多「棒」啊
Well, this is awesome.
以后咱们改变一下吧
You know what? New plan.
从现在开始 我们就呆车里
From now on, we just stay in the van.
派一个小妹子去替我们办事
and send in the 90-pound girl.
迪恩 地球上的大嘴怪都认识我们
Dean, every chomper on earth knows our face.
你猜这楼里会有多少大嘴怪
How many do you think are in that building?
我们连大厅都过不去
We wouldn't make it past the lobby.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
但我就是不喜欢
Doesn't mean I got to be happy about.
派个美眉校探去办事
sending in freaking Veronica Mars.
她会没事的
She'll be fine…
否则我们就冲进去
or we'll go in.
能冲多远冲多远 这才对
We'll get as far as we can. Damn right.
伙计们
Hey, guys.
我正把挖掘相关的全部文件发给你们
Sending you all the flagged dig files now.
查理 你真是个天才
Charlie, you are a genius!
我知道 真没办法
I know. It's a problem.
见鬼
Damn it.
好啊 皮特
Hey, Pete!
看来我们都急着交差
Guess we're both on deadline, huh?
进展如何
How's it going?
很好啊
Good, good.
过几个小时我就能把完整的进程报告给你了
I'll give you a full progress report in a few hours.
很好
Great.
别迟了 懂吗
Hit that deadline, right?
要什么就告诉我
Well, holler if you need anything.
你们还在吗
Hey, guys, you still there?
发生什么了
Yeah. What the hell was that?
我的经理过来了 他是怪物
Oh, just my manager, the monster.
快走
Leave.
不行 我得装成没事人
I can't. I got to act normal.
我告诉他我在工作 传完文件再说吧
I told him I was working. Let's just finish this.
你们看到了吗
Are you seeing this?
看起来迪克几天前停手不挖了
It looks like Dick stopped digging days ago.
为什么
Why?
因为他找到了他要的东西
Guess he found what he was looking for.
- 你能查查吗 - 早开始了
- Can you check? - Way ahead of you.
我在看出行记录和花费
Looking at travel reports, expenses…
有了
Here we go.
上周从伊朗发来一个手提箱
Something in his suitcase left Iran last week.
过去三天一直用装甲车和私人飞机运送
Spent the last 72 hours in armored cars and private planes.
不管这是什么 今晚迪克就去收货了
Whatever it is, it's coming here for Dick tonight.
那这是什么鬼东西
So, w-what the hell is it?
不知道 但他很迫切想拿到它
I don't know. Whatever it is, he wants it bad,
那我们就要拿到它 没得说
which means we got to grab it, end of story.
飞机会在附近私人机场降落
Well, it's landing at a private airport near here …
见鬼 就是现在
Crap … right about now.
他差人去拿了
A courier's set to pick it up.
确切的降落时间是多少
What's the exact landing time?
42分钟后 你们来得及吗
42 minutes. Can you make it?
尽量吧
We can try.
好了 查理 还有件事
Uh, all right, Charlie, one more favor,
做完赶快出来
and then get the hell out of there.
太棒了
Outstanding.
你一拿到箱子就会给我电话吧
And you'll call as soon as the package is in hand?
当然 我在等了
Absolutely. I'm here waiting.
事实上 我还能去吃点零食
In fact, I've got time for a light snack.
你好 查理
Hey, Charlie.
我正想找你
I was hoping I'd find you here.
- 抱歉 - 小心点
- Sorry. - Watch it.
现在怎么办
So now what?
我找这个已经找了很久很久了
I've been looking for this for a very, very long time.
这会是谁干的呢
Now, who could have done that?
他差人去拿了
A courier's set to pick it up.
- 确切的降落时间是多少 - 42分钟后
- What's the exact landing time? - 42 minutes.
- 你们来得及吗 - 尽量吧
- Can you make it? - We can try.
好了 查理 还有件事
Uh, all right, Charlie, one more favor,
做完赶快出来
and then get the hell out of there.
- 你需要什么 - 拖延的时间
- What do you need? - More time.
那就让我争取更多的时间
Then let's get you some.
（紧急货物延迟）
旅行部在给迪克发邮件
Travel department's e-mailing Dick.
手提箱还在路上
Suitcase still en route,
但是受天气影响 会晚到三十分钟
but diverted by weather and will be 30 minutes late.
我把关于你们的内容从硬盘里清除
I'll finish mopping you guys off the drive.
然后就闪人
and get the hell out of dodge.
安全后打给我们
Call us when you're clear.
到了边境给你们发短信 兄弟
Text you from the border, bro.
- 抱歉 - 小心点
- Sorry. - Watch it.
小心点
Watch it.
你好 查理
Hey, Charlie.
我正想找你
I was hoping I'd find you here.
你好 罗曼先生
Um, hey, Mr. Roman.
别这么生疏 喊我迪克
Please. Dick.
皮特 我们没事
Pete, we're good here.
你去吃点东西吧
Why don't you go grab a bite?
给我看看你找到了什么
Show me what you found.
现在怎么办
So now what?
看看我们拿到了什么
See what we've won.
我们…是不是就偷了一大块红黏土
Did we just…steal a-a hunk of red clay?
问得好
That's a good question.
我们先逃出几千里再想这个问题吧
Why don't we answer that a few thousand miles away from here, though?
查理在哪呢
Where is Charlie?
没什么和我公司有关的内容吗
So there's nothing about my company?
那萨姆或是迪恩呢
How about a Sam or a Dean?
对不起 你说谁
I'm sorry, who?
萨姆和迪恩 温彻斯特两兄弟
Sam and Dean winchester.
查查看 好吗
Give it a little peek, would you?
迪克·罗曼
Dick Roman.
冷静 姑娘就在这
Come on. The girl's right there.
考虑考虑她
Worry about her.
是我感觉有问题 还是这里温度骤降了十度
Is it me, or did it just drop 10 degrees in here?
是有点冷飕飕的
It's a bit nippy, yeah.
我会让维修部门检修空调
I'll have maintenance check the A.C.
我不能让你冻着了 对吧
I can't have you cold, now, can I?
你这个可悲的…
You miserable…
该死的 鲍比 别激动
Damn it, Bobby, come on.
（无匹配对象）
没有关于温彻斯特兄弟的内容
Nothing about those Winchesters.
如果硬盘上的东西被删除了
If items were deleted from the drive,
你能看出来吗
would you be able to tell?
如果删得好就看不出来
Not if they were deleted properly.
他们很狡猾
Well, they're crafty.
把所有数据发给我
Have all the data sent to me.
没问题
Of course.
说真的 你怎么做到的
So, really, how did you do it?
做什么
Uh, do what?
你攻下了不破之坚
You broke the unbreakable.
你是怎么想的
What's the thought process?
跟我说说 不许说行话
Walk me through it, and ix-nay the jargon.
没什么是不可攻破的 真的
Um…nothing's unbreakable, really.
滴水石穿 没什么是安全的
Nothing's safe if you poke at it long enough.
没什么是安全的 我喜欢
Nothing's safe. I like that.
但你这是答非所问啊 查理
But that isn't what I'm asking, Charlie.
你的灵气 是万里挑一的
Your spark … it's one in a million.
相信我 人一旦有了灵气
Believe me, but when you got it,
能发明枪 iPad和病毒
you invent guns and iPads and viruses,
能变得相当聪明
and, holy crap, you can be crafty.
查理 这到底是什么
What is that, Charlie?
我可以把你脑子里的东西都喂给别人
'Cause I can feed every fact in your brain to someone else,
他们还是不能像你这样
they still wouldn't be able to be you.
我大概是无法复制的
I guess you can't clone me.
这可真让我生气呢
Don't think that doesn't piss me off.
是我
Yes.
好极了 带到我办公室来
Fantastic. Bring it up to my office.
我马上就到
I'll be right there.
我们可能有发现
I think we're on to something here.
待在这里 我马上就回来
Stay here, will you? I'll be back in two shakes.
看来还真没什么是安全的
Nothing is safe, apparently.
立刻封锁大楼
Lock the building down now.
别跑啊 查理
Hold on there, Charlie.
迪恩 他也是怪物
Dean, he's one of them!
这样就说得通了
That would explain it.
孩子 你跟错人了
You're hanging with the wrong crowd, kiddo.
别急啊 迪克
Not so fast, Dick.
好吧 够了 出来吧
All right, enough! Show yourself.
像真正的怪物那样干一架吧
Let's do this like real monsters.
再来一次啊 真痒痒
You got to do that again. That tickled.
迪恩 快走 快走
Dean, come on. Come on!
查理 跟我们说话 你还好吗
Charlie, talk to us. You okay?
不好
No.
你们为什么没杀死他
Why didn't you kill him?
因为我们现在还杀不了他
'Cause we can't yet.
但我们一定会杀了他
But we will.
杀大Boss总得用特别武器
The really evil ones always need a special sword.
好吧 我现在要晕了
Oh, okay. I'm gonna pass out now.
因为他们拿去了
Because they have it!
在他们弄明白是怎么回事之前拿回来
Now get it back, before they figure the damn thing out!
求你了先生 别逼我自噬
Please, sir, d-don't bid me.
自噬
Bid you?!
我干嘛要浪费一顿美餐
Why would I waste a perfectly good meal?
- 谢谢 - 谢谢
- Thank you. - Thanks.
对了 我把那个破瓶子扔在后座了
I left your dumb flask on the backseat, by the way.
最差劲的幸运符了
Worst good-luck charm ever.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢
Thanks.
那个 我们对你的感激之情无以言表
So listen, um, we can't thank you enough.
其实你们可以表
Actually, you can.
永远不要再找我了 行吗
Never contact me again, like, ever. Deal?
行
Deal.
低调点 懂吗
Keep your head down out there, okay?
我又不是第一次销声匿迹
This ain't the first time I've disappeared.
你以为我真名就是查理·布兰博利
You think my name is really Charlie Bradbury?
拜托
Please.
拯救世界的人 祝你们好运
So, good luck saving the world.
再见啦 贱人们
Peace out, bitches.
她有点像我永远也不想要的妹妹
She's kind of like the little sister I never wanted.
我们得谈谈
We got to talk.
你是说趁现在没有鬼在旁边吗
Well, you mean before we get back to the car and the flask?
对
Exactly.
在大厅里到底发生了什么 迪恩
So, what the hell happened back in the lobby, Dean?
伙计 如果我有机会
Man, if I had a free shot,
也会痛扁迪克一顿
I'd have bitch-slapped the hell out of Dick.
我知道 但是 查理手臂受伤了
Yeah, but, I mean, Charlie got her freaking arm broken.
他不是故意的
He didn't mean to do it.
对啊
Exactly.
他失控了 不是因为迪克
He's not in control, not about Dick.
怨魂就是这个样子
That was vengeful-spirit crap.
我知道 但他还是鲍比
I know. But it's still Bobby.
但是如果他真的走到这一步 他就不再是他了
But if he really goes there, he won't be anymore,
我们也不能把他拉回来了
and then we won't be able to pull him back.
那我们要怎么办呢
And then what are we supposed to do?
我懂
I know.
我们先搞清楚偷来的是什么
Look, let's just figure out what that thing we stole is,
然后再去想怎么处理鲍比的事
and then we'll figure out what the hell to do with Bobby.